studentuniverse.com 2015-03-15

# StudentUniverse | Students - Privacy Policy

Our privacy policy is very important to us and governs our actions regarding your information at StudentUniverse.com, Inc. This document will tell you what information we collect from you, what we are going to do with the information, and your rights concerning the information. The information we receive depends on what you do when you visit our site.

If you visit our site to browse or read content, we use cookies (see below) to match your requests to a session, so we can remember if/when you logged on, and what products you are searching for. We log and track session data information to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, and to make our site more useful.

If you visit our site to make a purchase, our check-out process requires you to provide us with contact information (like your name and address), unique identifiers (like your email address), and demographic information (like your zip code and age).

We use your contact information from the account registration form to send you information about your purchases and promotional material (if you chose to allow us to). Your contact information is also used to contact you when necessary. You have the option of not receiving future mailings (see the choice/opt-out section below).

Unique identifiers (such as email addresses) are collected to verify your identity as a student or faculty member by us and/or our partners. We do not share this data with anyone except agencies that verify identity or student enrollment. Specifically, we and/or our partners validate your eligibility for certain offers based on your age or status as a student or faculty member. StudentUniverse.com, Inc and/or its partners reserves the right to use automated calling systems for delivering urgent information regarding your purchase and/or enrollment verification process. Financial information (such as credit card numbers) that we collect is used to bill customers for products and services.

We realize the sensitive nature of this information, and guard this information very carefully.

**Cookies**

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies, but we do not store your personal data in those cookies. Rather, we use cookies to collect and store non-personal data, such as the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet (for example, yahoo.com or princeton.edu); the Internet protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using; the browser software you use and your operating system; the date and time you access our site; and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site.

Some of our business partners, including Google, use cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) on our site to measure advertising effectiveness, show our adds on other sites, and serve ads based on your prior visits to our website, but we have no access to or control over these cookies and action tags. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can edit your browser options to block them in the future. If you would like more information about this practice and your choices, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp).

**Sharing Information**

No personally identifiable information will be shared with our partners except as part of an explicit transaction- for example, providing your customer data to the airline on which you've purchased a ticket or a partner for verification of your student/faculty enrollment or youth status. However, some of your information may be shared with third parties on an anonymous basis (but that information will not be sufficient to permit the recipient to identify you).

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy companies or assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that StudentUniverse.com, Inc or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information could be one of the transferred assets.

Except as set forth in the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy, we will not willfully disclose personal data about you to any third party without first receiving your permission. Failure to abide by the terms of use can forfeit your rights as described in our privacy policy.

**Spam**

We take extreme efforts to not involve ourselves with junk mail companies. Our mail is as targeted as we can make it, and we allow you to opt out at any time. If you feel we aren't living up to our promise, please  send us an email%7D).

We occasionally run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like your email address). We use contact data from our contests to alert winners of their status, and to send users information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. Users have the option of not receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

**Security**

We follow industry standards for credit card transactions to make sure your information stays yours. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology, which is widely used and respected across the industry. SSL encrypts your name, address, telephone number and credit card information before they are transmitted across the Internet, so you can feel safe about doing business with us.

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification and unlawful destruction or accidental loss. All employees who have access to, or are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect our visitors' personal data.

**Children's Guidelines**

Children under 15 are not permitted to create an account at StudentUniverse.com, Inc. We do not knowingly collect personal data from children. Our younger visitors may visit the site and read content, but only account holders over the age of 17 may buy products.

**Choice/Opt-Out**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

If you want to remove your information from our database, to not receive future communications, or to no longer receive our service, you can opt-out online on our homepage by clicking on "Get our DealAlerts" and completing the opt-out form, or send us an email%7D).

Mouseflow requires that we make our users aware that some visitor sessions are recorded, and Mouseflow prohibits using this service for recording personal or financial information. Users who don’t want to be recorded can opt out [here](http://mouseflow.com/opt-out). Read Mouseflow's [privacy policy](http://mouseflow.com/privacy/) for more information.

**Correct/Update**

You can correct or update your account profile information at any time by going to My Account and signing in to your existing account.

**Partner Websites**

This site contains links to other websites. StudentUniverse.com, Inc is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites.

**Contacting the Website**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with StudentUniverse.com, Inc on this website, send us an email%7D) or you can contact:  
StudentUniverse  
130 Turner Street  
Suite 530  
Waltham, MA 02453
